"Hoshimi Productions"
My heart is beating so fast.
There must be something...
Are you okay?
Thanks...
She seemed really cool...
"Hoshimi Productions"
Thank you very much!
All right next, #4...
Huh?!
Yes.
I'm #4, Kotono Nagase.
Nagase...?
H-Hey!
All right, come on in.
Kotono Nagase... By any chance...
I'm Mana Nagase's sister.
Mana's...?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
You're Mr. Shinji Saegusa, right?
You managed my sister from the beginning.
So what?
Please guide me as you did her.
I'm determined to make it through
any harsh training.
For this audition, I'm leaving
everything up to this guy.
I'm Kohei Makino.
I'll be in charge if you pass the audition.
You won't be in charge, Mr. Saegusa?
Of course we'll take care of you as the agency.
But Makino will be your direct manager.
First, let me ask you this:
Why do you want to become an idol?
I'm Mana Nagase's sister.
Isn't that enough of a reason?
I want to stand at the top of the Venus Program.
That's my goal.
"Singing"
"Script Reading"
Thank you very much.
"Posing"
"Dancing"
Have a seat.
I'll judge you on how you judge the auditioners!
All right next, #4...
Yes.
I'm #4, Kotono Nagase.
Nagase...?
H-Hey!
Why would she leave?
What's going on?
It's nothing...
If you pass, we'll have you
move into the company dorms.
Is that all right?
I'm able to commute from home.
It's our policy.
We want you to utilize what you gain
from living with other members
and deepening your understanding
for each other.
Members?
"Hoshimi Productions
Newcomer Discovery Project"
We're thinking of forming a group
for this upcoming project.
My sister was a solo artist.
My sister made it all the way to the
Next Venus Grand Prix finals by herself.
I'd like to be a solo artist, too.
You're...
I see.
Still, I don't plan to change
anything about this project.
If you can't agree to the terms,
you're more than welcome to pull out
before the results come in.
This concludes today's audition.
The results will be mailed out at a later date.
Do you have any questions for me?
I don't.
Excuse me...
Miss Haruko, what is it?
Wow!
Is this a studio?
Who is this?
She just came into our office,
so I assumed she was an auditioner...
She's the last one for the morning half.
What's your number?
My number?
Where am I right now?
We're a talent agency.
Talent...
Like, for idols?
That's right.
You're the girl from earlier!
So, you're going to become an idol?
It hasn't been decided yet.
The audition just ended.
Audition...
I see.
I'm sorry, it was my misunderstanding.
Come on, let's go.
Actually... May I audition, too?
You're supposed to pass
a screening before that--
You.
What's your name?
Huh?
What?
It's Sakura Kawasaki.
I'm able to tell what's important
and necessary for me.
What do you mean by that?
My heart lets me know.
It directs me to places and to take action.
My heart's never let me down before.
So, that's why you're here?
Yes!
My beating heart led me here
and I bumped into her.
My heart hasn't stopped pounding ever since!
It must be telling me to become an idol!
You gotta be kidding me.
You have no idea how many girls
are working hard to get into this world.
can't even get a chance...
This isn't a world you can enter
with such a ridiculous reason.
It's not ridiculous. This is what I believe.
I believe in my heart.
As she said, the idol world is a severe place.
Nowadays, your ability gets
quantified by the Venus Program.
There's a clear split between
winners and losers,
so you can say it's become
as harsh as ever.
We're doing this audition to judge whether you
got what it takes to survive in such a world.
Even if you sign with us, there's
no guarantee that you will succeed.
Now, do you still want to audition?
Yes!
So what can you do?
I can sing!
Will you sing for us now?
Yes!
♬ The story begins now ♬
♬ Like dancing flower petals ♬
♬ Let's hurry and run towards
the future with light steps! ♬
♬ The glory I dreamed about ♬
♬ In order to achieve it ♬
♬ I'll keep my face up ♬
♬ Face forward ♬
♬ Ready! ♬
♬ I make my wish through
this song and go forward ♬
♬ First step ♬
Oh my goodness.
You sounded just like Mana.
I wasn't good at singing when I was little.
But one day, I woke up, being able to sing!
Yeah, I know.
Makino?
Why did you run off like that earlier?
Seeing Kotono surprised me.
Still...
I wasn't expecting it.
And...
When I think about how much grief
I put her through...
I felt too ashamed...
But I never thought Kotono
would aim to become an idol.
She's matured a lot since I last saw her, too.
--But you came back to check on her anyway...
--It's not like that.
I wanted to leave Kotono up to you, Makino.
But then I heard that girl's singing...
Sakura Kawasaki's?
Yup. It got me really curious...
So I came back.
I thought her singing sounded a lot like yours.
Really? I can't tell myself.
You knew about Kotono and didn't tell me.
You're the one who chose
not to look at the resumes.
Still...
Mana's biological sister and a
mysterious girl with Mana's voice...
So what's your verdict?
I bet you're getting a kick
out of this, Mr. Saegusa.
You're the one responsible.
Yes.
"Kotono Nagase
Confidential
Audition Results
DO NOT BEND"
"Acceptance Letter
'Newcomer Discovery Project' Results
Thank you for applying to the
'Newcomer Discovery Project.'
Kotono!
Looking forward to working with you!
You, too.
Idoly Pride.
"Hoshimi Productions"
I'm Kotono Nagase.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm Sakura Kawasaki.
I look forward to working with you!
Makino is in charge of both of you.
There will be many challenges ahead, but I hope
to work hard and conquer them together.
Welcome aboard.
Thank you!
Makino used to be Mana's assistant manager.
What?
Mana's the one who brought Makino here, right?
She did?
Well, it's a long story...
It just so happened that we sat next to
each other in class, so it was easy to ask.
Um... Kotono's sister... Is it by any chance...?
Yeah, I'll explain later.
Now, I'll give you both a tour of the office.
You can leave your things there.
Okay!
So that's the story.
Kotono is Mana's...!
Anyway, I heard about your
health condition from your parents...
Yes.
I give up!
I'm no good at all.
You never break out of the pose.
It's impressive, Kotono!
I do basic training regularly.
I see!
As for me...
I was never the athletic type.
Do you think you can really make it like that?
Yup!
I believe in what I felt in my heart that day.
Did they tell you about me?
Yup, from Mr. Makino.
What did you think?
I was surprised!
Kotono, you're the Mana Nagase--
I mean, Miss Mana's little sister.
Even I know who she is, when I
don't know much about idols.
You sang my sister's song at the audition.
Yup! I really like that song.
But what a coincidence that this was her agency!
If we were to make our debut,
does that make us Miss Mana's juniors?
She's not here anymore.
Kotono...
Your regular lessons will start tomorrow.
Yes!
And you'll be moving into the dorms soon,
so be prepared.
Understood!
You'll meet the other members soon, too.
I can't wait!
Thank you for today!
I'm so curious about the other members!
Aren't you?
Not really.
I wanted to be a solo artist originally.
I see.
Miss Mana was, too, right?
Hey, Big Sister...
Who are they?
Big Sister...?
I've decided that I want to be in the industry,
become an idol!
That came out of nowhere.
It can't be that easy to be--
Sure it is!
I was scouted by a famous
producer the other day!
I'm home.
Where's Big Sister?
She said it's another late night at work.
What? Kotono said that?
She thinks your work is getting between you two.
Will you come see my performance
at the finals tomorrow?
You want me to witness your victory?
No, there's a song I want you to hear.
Since you became an idol,
it's been such a nuisance for me.
All they talk about at school is you.
People hassle me for your autograph
or a chance to meet you...
--Sorry.
--Don't apologize.
If this were the case...
Yes, this is Nagase.
Yes... Yes, I'm her younger sister.
What...?
A diary...?
Big Sister...
Kotono!
See you later! I'm this way!
Can't wait for tomorrow!
You don't want me to tell your sister?
What?
"Your sister has unfinished business,
so she's still lingering around as a ghost"?
I would word it a little differently...
There's no way you could tell her.
Kotono's probably trying
to become an idol for me.
She's trying to achieve the thing I left undone.
If Kotono's the one who'll take over my dream...
I can never be happier.
Mana...
Since I disappeared,
she got motivated to do this.
That's why...
If she actualizes my dream for me,
maybe I can finally rest in peace.
"Hoshimi Productions"
Field training?
Yeah, go get ready.
In front of the train station...?
That's right.
This place...
Let's try singing here.
What? But there's people around...
You'll eventually sing in front
of even more people.
It's better to get used to that now.
But singing on stage and
singing at a place like this is--
The same.
The stage isn't something that's provided.
Wherever you sing becomes the stage.
This is the place where a certain idol
often came to practice singing.
Could that "certain idol" be...?
I'll do it.
Kotono?!
I would watch her, too, sometimes.
My sister singing here...
All right, so let's get singing.
I'll be watching from over there.
What?! Um... Mr. Makino...
Sakura, are you ready?
Y-Yeah!
♬ I've encountered something I love
from the bottom of my heart ♬
♬ For the very first time ♬
♬ This racing heart isn't a coincidence ♬
♬ It's a sign I chose the right path ♬
♬ A healing sakura-colored wind ♬
♬ Encourages me to push forward ♬
♬ An unknown path ♬
♬ I wonder what awaits ♬
♬ I'm filled with a fluttering sensation ♬
Kotono...
♬ The story begins now ♬
♬ Like dancing flower petals ♬
--♬ Let's hurry and run towards
the future with light steps! ♬
--Sakura's voice... It really sounds like her.
--♬ Let's hurry and run towards
the future with light steps! ♬
♬ The glory I dreamed about ♬
♬ In order to achieve it ♬
♬ I'll keep my face up ♬
♬ Face forward ♬
♬ Ready! ♬
♬ I make my wish through this song
and go forward ♬
♬ First step! ♬
Wow!
--They remind me of Mana.
--Yeah!
People called her "that girl after school."
You look just like Mana.
Y-Yes.
I'm her sister.
Oh, really?
Your singing makes me think of Mana.
What?
Best of luck to you both!
Thank you very much!
Does my singing really sound like Miss Mana's?
You're not trying to imitate her?
I would listen to her songs, but I never
intentionally tried to sound like her.
You do sound like her.
It's the color... or the feel of your voice.
Even I think so, as her sister.
Really...
Wow, it's big!
It used to be some kind of recreation facility.
Your things should be delivered already.
Oh, Mr. Makino.
Are they...?
I want to introduce them,
so let's gather in the living room.
I'm Saki Shiraishi.
A third-year in high school.
I'm probably the eldest of the members.
I'm her sister, Chisa Shiraishi.
It's nice to meet you.
I am the one and only Suzu Narumiya.
The name Narumiya probably rung a bell for you.
I am the daughter of the
prestigious Narumiya family.
What is with the pathetic reaction?!
You can be a little more impressed, you know?!
Miss Saki seems more high-class to me.
I heard that!
I'm Shizuku Hyodo.
I'm Sakura Kawasaki, nice to meet you.
I'm Kotono Nagase.
Nagase? Are you...?
I'm her sister.
I see.
You look like her.
Huh? What is it?
Go ahead and pick an open room.
The room next to me should be open, too.
What's the matter?
Um... Mr. Makino, will you be staying here, too?
Yeah, I moved here a little while ago
as sort of a supervisor...
All girls can be a little--
Um... What's wrong?
Huh?
Why do I have to stay in a shed?
Well, of course!
And plus it suits you, Makino.
What does that mean?
Don't worry, I'll watch over
the girls in the dorm.
I don't get it.
It seems like it'll be lively
and fun around here.
Huh?! What is this?! How do I stop it?
What?! Oh, no!
Wait! W-W-Wait a minute! Hold on! Please!
K-Kotono! Help me!
"The Reason We Stand Here"